yellowee.com 2012-12-05

# Yellowee :: Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we’ve developed this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy covers the collection and use of personal information, such as your name, address, email, credit card information, and billing information (“Personal Information”), that may be collected by Yellowee Inc. or any of its other owned and operated websites, anytime you interact with us, such as when you search for information on any of our websites, purchase our advertising services, join our publisher network, or call our customer service associates (collectively, Yellowee’ “Services”). This Privacy Policy describes our information practices, including what type of information is gathered, how the information is used and for what purposes, to whom we disclose the information, and how we safeguard your Personal Information. It also describes the choices available to you regarding Yellowee’s use of your Personal Information and the steps you can take to access this information and to request that we correct or delete it.

Your continued participation on the Yellowee Services indicates your acceptance of this Privacy Policy and of the collection, use, disclosure, management and storage of your Personal Information as described below. This Privacy Policy will remain in full force and effect (with such changes as we may make to this Privacy Policy) as long as you are a user of the Yellowee Services, even if your use of or participation in any particular Service expires, ceases, or is suspended or deactivated for any reason.

**Yellowee Inc. Privacy Officer**

If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, or would like to update or delete your Personal Information, please contact us. If you email us, please be sure to write “PRIVACY INQUIRY” in the subject line of your email. Yellowee will respond to legitimate inquiries within 30 days.

Yellowee **  
** ATTN: Privacy Officer  
205 - 11 Morris Drive  
Dartmouth, Nova Scotia, Canada B3B 1M2

Phone: 902.431.4847  
Email: privacy@yellowee.com

**Why We Collect Personal Information**

We collect Personal Information to help us deliver a superior level of service. It enables us to give you convenient access to our search services, advertising services and publisher services, and helps us keep you updated on special offers, news, and the latest information on Yellowee products and services that you might like to hear about.

**Information We Collect & How We Use It**

There are a number of situations in which your Personal Information may help us give you better service.

**Information Automatically Collected by our Website**

Like many websites, we collect and analyze certain user behavior on our website and store it in log files. This information includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, referring/exit pages, the date & time, and search queries. We also collect information regarding user activities on our website. We use this information to analyze website traffic, improve the performance of our search Services, improve our geo-targeted advertising services, administer the website and prevent fraud. This helps us to determine how best to provide useful information to users and to understand which parts of our website and Services are of most interest to them.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

We track user behavior and use of our Services through the use of cookies and web beacons. A “cookie” is a small text file that a website can place on your computer’s hard drive in order, for example, to collect information about your activities on the website or to make it easier to use certain website functions. The cookie transmits this information back to the website’s computer. Many users do not know that “cookies” are being placed on their computers when they visit a website. If you want to know when this happens, or prevent it from happening, you can set your browser to warn you when a website attempts to place a “cookie” on your computer.

We use cookies to improve the quality of our Service by storing user preferences and tracking user trends, such as how people search and which advertisements they click on. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your computer for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file.

We use cookies on our website to provide our Service, including without limitation, in the following ways:

When you initially REGISTER AS A USER OR BUSINESS OWNER on Yellowee, we use a cookie to remember your user preferences. If you have checked the “Remember me” checkbox and you have identified yourself, the cookie allows you to skip having to identify yourself again. Please do not check the “Remember me” box if you are using a shared computer.

We use cookies to track when a search user clicks on a sponsored listing, and in some cases we use cookies and web beacons to determine whether the click resulted in an actual purchase of products or services from the advertiser’s site. This information is used to determine the effectiveness of our advertising Services.

We also use cookies to analyze how visitors, in the aggregate, use our website, in order to make our website as useful as possible for them. We do not use cookies to collect or store personally identifiable information.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some of our Services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.

We also use web beacons (a small transparent image, iframe, script, object or other transparent tag embedded in a web page) on some of our web pages and advertising Services. Whenever the user opens the page with a browser, the web beacon or tag is requested from the server storing it, allowing the server to take notice of the download. As a result, our servers (or our website analytics company’s servers) are informed of when the web page has been viewed.

**Third Party Advertisers, Your Opt-out Rights**

We use third-party companies to serve advertisements and collect non-personally identifiable information when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to our website and other sites in order to provide advertisements on our website, other sites and other forms of media about goods and services that may be of interest to you.  If you would like more information about the practices of some of these third party advertising companies and learn which of these companies allow you to opt-out of this type of information collection, please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp "NAI").

**User Information**

If you advertise your business on Yellowee, we will use the personally identifying information you provide (your company name, billing information and contact information) to contact you about your account when necessary. We use this information only for billing purposes, to fill your orders, and to deliver the services you have requested. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.

In some of our email messages, web pages and search results we use a “click-through URL” linked to content on the Yellowee website. When a recipient clicks one of these URLs, they pass through a web server before arriving at the destination webpage. We track this click-through data to help us determine interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of our customer communications. If you prefer not to be tracked simply avoid clicking text or graphic links in the email.

**Contact Us**

If you provide Personal Information to us by sending us email, letters or faxes or by calling us, we will use that information to respond to your question or request for information. We may ask for your Personal Information when you’re discussing a service issue on the phone with a customer services associate, registering to become a user, participating in an online survey, or purchasing our products and services. At such times, we may collect Personal Information relevant to the situation, such as your name, email address, phone number, and contact preferences; your credit card information; and information relating to a support or service issue.

**Surveys**

We may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys. If you participate, we may request certain Personal Information from you. Participation in these contests or surveys is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and email address), and demographic information (such as zip code). We use the survey data to improve our Services, and may publicize the results as a public service. The publicized results will not include any personally identifiable information without your consent.

We may use a third party service provider to conduct these contests or surveys. While this third party will have access to your Personal Information, it will be subject to confidentiality and only as necessary to conduct the services we have requested from them. We will not share the personally identifiable information you provide through a contest or survey with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice.

**When We Share Your Personal Information**

We do not sell or barter your contact or Personal Information to anyone.

There are times when Yellowee makes certain Personal Information about you available to companies that Yellowee has a strategic relationship with or that perform work for Yellowee to provide services to you on our behalf. These companies may help us perform various business functions, including without limitation, improving the targeting of our advertisements across our network, fulfilling customer orders, processing payments, managing and enhancing customer data, providing customer service, assessing your interest in our Services, or conducting surveys. These companies are also obligated to protect your Personal Information in accordance with applicable law. Without such information being made available, it would be difficult for you to use our Services, receive customer service, provide us feedback to improve our Services, or access certain of our Services; and it would be difficult for us to continue improving our search and advertising Services.

We will also share your Personal Information if we have a good faith belief that we are required to do so by law, that doing so is necessary to cooperate with law enforcement agencies, comply with warrants or subpoenas served on Yellowee, enforce the Terms & Conditions, detect fraud, or otherwise protect the rights of Yellowee, its employees and users of the Services.

**How We Protect & Secure Your Personal Information**

We take administrative, electronic, technical, and physical precautions to safeguard and secure your Personal Information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.

The Yellowee Site uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption on all webpages where Personal Information is required, including but not limited to, our publisher and advertiser account pages. We also follow industry standards to provide security for your sensitive information once we receive it.

You can help protect your Personal Information by also taking precautions to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords often using a combination of letters and numbers, don’t disclose your account information or password to anyone else, and make sure you use a secure web browser.

Please be aware, however, that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. You should always use caution when submitting Personal Information online.

**Access to Your Personal Information**

We will provide you reasonable access and the ability to correct the Personal Information you have provided. You can help us ensure that your contact information and preferences are accurate, complete, and up to date by checking your online account. If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our Service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by making the change on your online account or by contacting us.

You can also request a copy of your Personal Information and your account history by contacting us. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

**Links to Other Websites**

Our website includes links to thousands of other websites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Yellowee. Yellowee does not control the websites of third parties that are linked from our Services, and is not responsible for information included in those services. If you submit Personal Information to any of those websites, your information is subject to their privacy statements. Yellowee’s privacy statement applies only to its own Services, and does not apply to any other website. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any website you visit. Yellowee is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other websites.

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

If we change this Privacy Policy in ways that affect the personally identifying information we have collected through our website, we will post the updated Privacy Policy on this webpage to advise you of choices you may have as a result of those changes. Any changes made to this Privacy Policy will go into effect immediately, so please check back periodically to remain informed as to changes in the Privacy Policy.

**Privacy Statement Compliance**

If you feel that we have not complied with this privacy statement, please contact us using the information supplied above.

_UPDATED: April 3, 2012_
